<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<meta xmlns="http://exist-db.org/xquery/repo">
    <description>TEI Publisher: Processing Model Libraries</description>
    <author>Wolfgang Meier</author>
    <website>https://github.com/eeditiones/tei-publisher-lib.git</website>
    <status>stable</status>
    <license>GPLv3</license>
    <copyright>true</copyright>
    <type>library</type>
    <target />
    <note>Generated apps may fail after updating. Run .../myapp/modules/lib/regenerate.xql in browser or eXide once
        to update your ODDs.</note>
    <changelog>
        <change version="2.8.9">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Add support for transforming a docx package</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.8.8">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Added library module to generate a pm-config.xql based on ODD files used.</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.8.7">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>If changes to an ODD introduce XQuery syntax errors, don't overwrite the existing XQuery module.
                    Instead store it with suffix .invalid.xql for reference but keep the old module.
                </li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.8.6">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Avoid line breaks before footnote numbers. This mainly affects TEI Publisher 6,
                    which uses a different library for the footnote popups.
                </li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.8.5">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Fix compatibility with eXist 5.3.0: remove conflicting function declarations, which now cause an error</li>
                <li>Do not recompile ODDs automatically as this causes a security issue with the new permissions setup</li>
                <li>Output alternate as template within pb-popover to avoid invalid HTML for block-level content</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.8.4">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Generated footnote popups will now use pb-popover (with TEI Publisher 6), 
                which provides better positioning</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.8.3">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Enhanced docx to TEI import</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.8.2">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>add optional parameter 'persistent' to alternate behaviour: if true, popups will appear on click
                and stay until dismissed</li>
                <li>use internal numbering for alternate IDs to avoid conflicts</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.8.1">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Update backward compatibility for older eXist versions: Last release v2.8.0 introduced breaking changes by using new functions for the `docx` module that are only supported by eXist 5.x.x versions and thus introduced a dependency to eXist 5.x.x. This release resolves the dependency by handling both new and deprecated functions.</li>
                <li>Increment version number for latest commits (44300a0, dc3625c) made within release 2.8.0</li>
                <li>Minor changes in `.gitignore` file: Exclude `.*` files by default, unless explicitly included.</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.8.0">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Update for compatibility with eXist 5.0</li>
                <li>Improve naming of template functions to avoid wrong calls</li>
                <li>Add target parameter for behaviour link</li>
                <li>Add TEI output mode and module for transforming docx to TEI</li>
                <li>Rename link parameter for behaviour link to "uri" for spec compliance; support old "link" as fallback</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.7.0">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Fix loading of external CSS from relative path</li>
                <li>HTML output: if a label is defined for a note or list item, output it directly. Adds "n" parameter to listItem.</li>
                <li>Implement alternate for LaTeX the same way as for FO: output alternate as footnote after default</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.6.0">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Faster loading of behaviour library by avoiding use of counter module where possible</li>
                <li>Support CSS styles for web to be loaded from external css via &lt;rendition source="myfile.css"/&gt;</li>
                <li>Use $get(.) to get the original source element for the current node. Used to fix computation of heading levels</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.5.0">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Support for templates and user-defined behaviours within the ODD</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.1.0">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Renditions defined in tei header were no longer applied</li>
                <li>Support definition of default elementSpec for elements and text nodes</li>
                <li>FO output: make sure to not produce an empty destination for internal and external links</li>
                <li>Fix internal references for LaTeX output</li>
                <li>Apply class to line breaks so they can be stiled via CSS</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
    </changelog>
    <permissions user="tei" group="tei" password="simple" mode="rw-rw-r--" />
</meta>