<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<meta xmlns="http://exist-db.org/xquery/repo">
    <description>TEI Publisher: Processing Model Libraries</description>
    <author>Wolfgang Meier</author>
    <website>http://gitlab.exist-db.org/tei-publisher/tei-publisher-lib</website>
    <status>stable</status>
    <license>GPLv3</license>
    <copyright>true</copyright>
    <type>library</type>
    <target/>
    <note>Generated apps may fail after updating. Run .../myapp/modules/lib/regenerate.xql in browser or eXide once
        to update your ODDs.</note>
    <changelog>
        <change version="2.8.0">
             <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                 <li>Update for compatibility with eXist 5.0</li>
                 <li>Improve naming of template functions to avoid wrong calls</li>
                 <li>Add target parameter for behaviour link</li>
                 <li>Add TEI output mode and module for transforming docx to TEI</li>
                 <li>Rename link parameter for behaviour link to "uri" for spec compliance; support old "link" as fallback</li>
             </ul>
         </change>
       <change version="2.7.0">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Fix loading of external CSS from relative path</li>
                <li>HTML output: if a label is defined for a note or list item, output it directly. Adds "n" parameter to listItem.</li>
                <li>Implement alternate for LaTeX the same way as for FO: output alternate as footnote after default</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.6.0">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Faster loading of behaviour library by avoiding use of counter module where possible</li>
                <li>Support CSS styles for web to be loaded from external css via &lt;rendition source="myfile.css"/&gt;</li>
                <li>Use $get(.) to get the original source element for the current node. Used to fix computation of heading levels</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.5.0">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Support for templates and user-defined behaviours within the ODD</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="2.1.0">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Renditions defined in tei header were no longer applied</li>
                <li>Support definition of default elementSpec for elements and text nodes</li>
                <li>FO output: make sure to not produce an empty destination for internal and external links</li>
                <li>Fix internal references for LaTeX output</li>
                <li>Apply class to line breaks so they can be stiled via CSS</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
    </changelog>
    <permissions user="tei" group="tei" password="simple" mode="rw-rw-r--"/>
</meta>
